Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - E
        - El Da Sensei - Crowd pleasa; Natural feel good, 2006; SR-14022; El Da Sensei (Box 255)
          Catalog # FB 2523; A-side Matrix # FB-2523-A
        - El Gran Combo - Historia musical de el gran combo de Puerto Rico (Disc one), 1982; SR-14023; El Gran Combo (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14024. Double album.
          Catalog # RCSLP-2029; A-side Matrix # COMBO-RC-2029-A
          Combo Records
        - El Gran Combo - Historia musical de el gran combo de Puerto Rico (Disc two), 1982; SR-14024; El Gran Combo (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14023. Double album.
          Catalog # RCSLP-2030; A-side Matrix # COMBO-RC-2030-A
        - El-P - Fandamstrumentals (Disc one), 2002; SR-14025; El-P (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14026; SR-14027. Triple album.
          Catalog # DJX33; A-side Matrix # DJX33-SIDE1A
          Definitive Jux
        - El-P - Fandamstrumentals (Disc two), 2002; SR-14026; El-P (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14025; SR-14027. Triple album.
        - El-P - Fandamstrumentals (Disc three), 2002; SR-14027; El-P (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14025; SR-14026. Triple album.
        - El Train - Action style, 1985; SR-14029; El Train (Box 255)
          Catalog # 12 WAR 3002; A-side Matrix # 12 WAR-3002-A
          Where Artists Record
        - Elaine & Ellen - The look of love, 1979; SR-14030; Elaine & Ellen (Box 255)
          Catalog # MK-97; A-side Matrix # MK-97-2 A
          Mercury
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Electra - Feels good (carrots & beets), 1982; SR-14031; Electra; Butler, Tara (Box 255)
          Catalog # EMDS-6527; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6527-A
          Emergency
        - Electric Boogiemen - Breakdancing, 1984; SR-14032; Electric Boogiemen (Box 255)
          Catalog # CARRERE 8332; A-side Matrix # 8332A
          Carrere
        - ELO - Time, 1981; SR-14033; ELO (Box 255)
          Catalog # FZ 37371; A-side Matrix # PAL-37371-1AD
          Jet Records
        - Electric Youngster - EP, 1998; SR-14034; Electric Youngster; Vanitas (Box 255)
          Catalog # Toxic002; A-side Matrix # TOXIC-002-A
          Toxic Records
          Germany
        - Electric Guitars - Wolfman Tap (extended version), 1983; SR-14035; Electric Guitars (Box 255)
          Catalog # 12 NAV 5; A-side Matrix # 12-NAV-5-A1
          Naive Records
        - Electronic - Getting away with it, 1990; SR-14036; Electronic (Box 255)
          Catalog # 0-21498; A-side Matrix # 0-21498-A SR1
        - Elegance - Vacances j'oublie tout, 1982; SR-14037; Elegance (Box 255)
          Catalog # 290 014; A-side Matrix # 222 29001 A
          Barclay
        - Elektrochemie LK - Schall remixes vol. II, 2000; SR-14038; Elektrochemie LK (Box 255)
          Catalog # CON 28; A-side Matrix # CON 28-A2
          Confused Recordings
        - Electrik, Dane - The beat goes on, SR-14039; Electrik, Dane (Box 255)
          Catalog # CK 01; A-side Matrix # CX 1589 A
          CC Records
        - Electrik, Funk - On a journey (I sing the funk electric), 1982; SR-14040; Electrik, Funk (Box 255)
          Catalog # PRL D 541; A-side Matrix # PRLD-541-A
          Prelude Records
        - Elektrik Sparks Band - You can't stop (the phrock), SR-14041; Elektrik Sparks Band (Box 255)
          Catalog # PPRT 823; A-side Matrix # PP-RT-823-A-RE
          Pretty Pearl Records
        - Elements Of Style - That's the kind of girl; Walking in harmony, 1991; SR-14042; Elements Of Style (Box 255)
          Catalog # V-56230; A-side Matrix # V-1-56230-Z2
          Wild Pitch Records
        - Elements of life - Molecular dreams (Disc two), 1994; SR-14043; Elements of life (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14044. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # OMWE-004; A-side Matrix # OMWE-004-C
          OMW (Oxygen Music Works)
        - Elements of life - Molecular dreams (Disc two), 1994; SR-14044; Elements of life (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14043. Multiple copies.
        - Elementz - Neon Verses EP, 2000; SR-14045; Elementz (Box 255)
          Catalog # DIFEP15; A-side Matrix # DIF-EP-15-A
          Different Drummer
          Birmingham, United Kingdom
        - Elementz - Elementz universe vol. 1, 2004; SR-14046; Elementz (Box 255)
          Catalog # EUE 001; A-side Matrix # EUE VOL001 A-1
          Elementz Universe Entertainment
        - Elephant Man - Backyard remixes, SR-14047; Elephant Man; Ward 21 (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14048. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BY127; A-side Matrix # BY-127-A
          Elephant Man
        - Elephant Man - Backyard remixes, SR-14048; Elephant Man; Ward 21 (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14047. Multiple copies.
        - Elephant Man - Log on!, 2002; SR-14049; Elephant Man (Box 255)
          Catalog # GAP005; A-side Matrix # GAP-005-A
        - Elgart, Charlie - Signs of life, 1988; SR-14050; Elgart, Charlie (Box 255)
          Catalog # 3045-1-N-A; A-side Matrix # 3045-1-N-A-10
          Novus
        - Eli's Second Coming - Heavenly; Why don'cha, 1977; SR-14051; Eli's Second Coming (Box 255)
          Catalog # TKD-69; A-side Matrix # TKD-69-A
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Elite Force - Cool like the man (remixes), 1977; SR-14052; Elite Force (Box 255)
          Catalog # FABR008T; A-side Matrix # FABR 008T-A1
          Fused & Bruised
        - Elli & Jacno - Chica Chica Bongo, 1984; SR-14053; Elli & Jacno (Box 255)
          Catalog # CBS 12.4517; A-side Matrix # 11-4517-2A-1
          CBS
          Netherlands
        - Duke Ellington And His Orchestra - Midnight in Paris, 1962; SR-14054; Duke Ellington And His Orchestra; Ellington, Duke (Box 255)
          Catalog # CL 1907; A-side Matrix # XLP-57328-1D
        - Duke Ellington And His Orchestra - The symphonic Ellington, 1963; SR-14055; Duke Ellington And His Orchestra; Ellington, Duke (Box 255)
          Catalog # R-6097; A-side Matrix # 10291-1C
        - Elliot, Missy - Teary eyed (Disc one), 2006; SR-14056; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14057. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 302092; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302092 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - Teary eyed (Disc two), 2006; SR-14057; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14056. Double album.
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Da real world (Disc one), 1999; SR-14058; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # ED-6148; A-side Matrix # ST-3W-6148-A
          EastWest Records America
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Da real world (Disc two), 1999; SR-14059; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # ED-6148; A-side Matrix # ST-3W-6148-C
        - Elliot, Missy - Back in the day, 2003; SR-14060; Elliot, Missy; Jay-Z (Box 255)
          Catalog # 67387-0; A-side Matrix # ST-E-67387 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - Teary eyed; Joy, 2005; SR-14061; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # PR 301896; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301896A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - We run this; Meltdown, 2005; SR-14062; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # PR 301031; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-3011031A-1
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Hot boyz, 1999; SR-14063; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # 0-63724; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-63724 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Beep me 911 (remix), 1998; SR-14064; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # ED-6078; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6078 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - Under construction (Disc one), 2002; SR-14065; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14066. Double album.
          Catalog # 62813-1; A-side Matrix # 62813-1-A
        - Elliot, Missy - Under construction (Disc two), 2002; SR-14066; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14065. Double album.
        - Sermon, Erick - React, 2002; SR-14067; Sermon, Erick; Redman (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14068; SR-14069. Different discs.
          Catalog # 80813-21221-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-21221-1A
          J Records
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Work it; P***ycat, 2002; SR-14068; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14067; SR-14069. Different discs; Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 67340-0; A-side Matrix # 0-67340 RE-1 A
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Work it; P***ycat, 2002; SR-14069; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14067; SR-14068. Different discs; Multiple copies.
        - Elliot, Missy - Teary eyed; Joy, 2005; SR-14070; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Supa dupa fly (the rain), 1997; SR-14071; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          Catalog # ED-6036; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6036 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - The cookbook (Disc one), 2005; SR-14072; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14073. Double album.
          Catalog # 83779-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-83779A-2
        - Elliot, Missy - The cookbook (Disc two), 2005; SR-14073; Elliot, Missy (Box 255)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14072. Double album.
        - Elliot, Missy - I'm really hot, 2004; SR-14074; Elliot, Missy (Box 256)
          Catalog # ED-6422; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6422 A1
        - Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor" - Supa dupa fly (the rain), 1997; SR-14075; Elliot, Missy "Misdemeanor"; Elliot, Missy (Box 256)
        - Elliot, Missy - Gossip folks, 2003; SR-14076; Elliot, Missy; Ludacris (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14077. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 67356-0; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6374A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - Gossip folks, 2003; SR-14077; Elliot, Missy; Ludacris (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14076. Multiple copies.
        - Elliot, Missy - Lose control, 2005; SR-14078; Elliot, Missy; Ciara; Fatman Scoop (Box 256)
          Catalog # PR 301982; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301982 A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - We run this; Meltdown, 2005; SR-14079; Elliot, Missy (Box 256)
          Catalog # PR 301031; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301031A-1
        - Elliot, Missy - Lose control; On & on, 2005; SR-14080; Elliot, Missy; Ciara; Fatman Scoop (Box 256)
          Catalog # PR 301785; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301785A-1
        - Ellis, Bobby - Shaka, 1984; SR-14081; Ellis, Bobby (Box 256)
          Catalog # DA 102; A-side Matrix # DA 102 A
          Dublab Records
          San Rafael, California
        - Ellis "D" - My Loleatta, 1987; SR-14082; Ellis "D" (Box 256)
          Catalog # MINIMAL-1; A-side Matrix # MIN-1-A
          Minimal Records
        - Ellis, Shirley - In action, 1964; SR-14083; Ellis, Shirley (Box 256)
          Catalog # CGL-3002; A-side Matrix # CGL 4 3002-A-2
          Congress
        - Ellis, Terry - What did I do to you?, 1996; SR-14084; Ellis, Terry (Box 256)
          Catalog # ED 5843; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5843-A-1
        - Emage - The choice is yours, 1994; SR-14087; Emage (Box 256)
          Catalog # 858 843-1DJ; A-side Matrix # 858-843-1-A
        - Emanon - The baby beat box, 1986; SR-14088; Emanon (Box 256)
          Catalog # PW 7403; A-side Matrix # PW-7403-A
          Pow Wow Records
        - Emanon - Susie, 1987; SR-14089; Emanon (Box 256)
          Catalog # PW 422; A-side Matrix # PW-422-A
        - Billy - Mix 2 - spotlight, 1994; SR-14090; Billy; Monique (Box 256)
          Catalog # 6WP0394; A-side Matrix # 6WP_0394_A
          Brazil
        - Embee - Power remix; Drop the bomb, 2000; SR-14091; Embee (Box 256)
          Catalog # SPLAZH030; A-side Matrix # SPLAZH 030 A
          Splash Recordings
          Essex, United Kingdom
        - EMF - I believe, 1991; SR-14092; EMF (Box 256)
          Catalog # V-56212; A-side Matrix # V-1-56212-RE1-Z1-DMM
        - EMF - Unbelievable (remix), 1990; SR-14093; EMF (Box 256)
          Catalog # 12RX 6273; A-side Matrix # 12 RX 6273 A-1-1-2
          Parlophone
        - EMF - Schubert dip, 1991; SR-14094; EMF (Box 256)
          Catalog # E1-96238; A-side Matrix # E1-1-9623E-Z1-DMM
          EMI USA
        - Eminem - Forgot about Dre; What's the difference;Make money; Bitch so wrong, 1999; SR-14095; Eminem; Dr. Dre; Hittman; Royce Da 5'9" (Box 256)
          Catalog # EM 406; A-side Matrix # EM406-A
          Aftermath Entertainment
        - Eminem - Curtain call: the hits (Disc one), 2005; SR-14096; Eminem (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14097. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005881-01; A-side Matrix # B0005881-01-LP1A
        - Eminem - Curtain call: the hits (Disc two), 2005; SR-14097; Eminem (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14096. Double album.
          Catalog # B0005881-01; A-side Matrix # B0005881-01-LP2A
        - Eminem - Superman, 2002; SR-14098; Eminem (Box 256)
          Catalog # INTR-10891-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10891-1A-RE1
        - Eminem - Bitch please II, 2000; SR-14099; Eminem; Dr. Dre; Snoop Dogg; Xzibit; Nate Dogg (Box 256)
          Catalog # INTR-10115-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10115-1
        - Eminem - Encore, 2004; SR-14100; Eminem (Box 256)
          Catalog # INTR-11281-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-11281-1-A
        - Eminem - The real Slim Shady, 2000; SR-14101; Eminem (Box 256)
          Catalog # 694973341; A-side Matrix # 694973341-A RE1
        - Eminem - Cleanin' out my closet, 2002; SR-14102; Eminem (Box 256)
          Catalog # INTR-10799-1; A-side Matrix # INTR-10799-1-A
        - Emotions - Rejoice, 1977; SR-14103; Emotions (Box 256)
          Catalog # PC 34762; A-side Matrix # PAL-34762-1L
        - Emotions - Turn it out; It's you, 1981; SR-14104; Emotions; Afterbach (Box 256)
          Catalog # AS 992; A-side Matrix # XSS 168214 1C
        - Emotions - Flowers; Best of my love, 1977; SR-14105; Emotions (Box 256)
          Catalog # SWAVE 10; A-side Matrix # SWAVE 10 A1
          Streetwave
        - Emotions - Flowers; Best of my love, 1977; SR-14106; Emotions (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14107. Multiple copies.
        - Emotions - Flowers; Best of my love, 1977; SR-14107; Emotions (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14106. Multiple copies.
        - Emperor Sly - Rockit, 1998; SR-14108; Emperor Sly (Box 256)
          Catalog # ZD 18; A-side Matrix # ZD 18-A1
          Zip Dog Records
          Chesham, United Kingdom
        - Emperors - Fantasy love, 1987; SR-14109; Emperors (Box 256)
          Catalog # IN 0304; A-side Matrix # SN 24205 SCFLE-IN 0300 A
          Inner Harbors Sounds Inc.
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Empire Bakuba - Bakuba show, 1987; SR-14110; Empire Bakuba (Box 256)
          Catalog # SYL 8338; A-side Matrix # 387L3-1A
          Syllart Production
          Paris, France
        - Empress Akelia - Apartheid is wrong, SR-14111; Empress Akelia (Box 256)
          Different Jacket
          Catalog # SJ 001; A-side Matrix # SJ 001-A
          Sing-Jay
        - En Vogue - Riddle, 2000; SR-14112; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # ED-6204; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6204 A-1
        - En Vogue - Don't let go (love), 1996; SR-14113; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # ED-5892; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5892-1-A
        - En Vogue - Time goes on, 1991; SR-14114; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # DMD 1748; A-side Matrix # 61223-61226-1
        - En Vogue - Riddle, 2000; SR-14115; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # 7559-67054-0; A-side Matrix # E7053TA1
        - En Vogue - Don't let go (love), 1996; SR-14116; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # ED-5877; A-side Matrix # ST 3D-65975-A1
        - En Vogue - Born to sing, 1990; SR-14117; En Vogue (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14118. Multiple copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # 82084-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-897681-A
        - En Vogue - Born to sing, 1990; SR-14118; En Vogue (Box 256)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14117. Multiple copies. Annotated.
        - En Vogue - Free your mind, 1992; SR-14119; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # 0-96128; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-63496-63497-1
        - En Vogue - Hold on, 1990; SR-14120; En Vogue (Box 256)
          Catalog # DMD 1452; A-side Matrix # STDM-58274-58275-58276-2
        - Enchantment - I know your hot spot; Only you, 1982; SR-14121; Enchantment (Box 256)
          Catalog # 44-03081; A-side Matrix # XSS-170283-1A
        - End Of The Weak - Black ops, 2002; SR-14122; End Of The Weak (Box 256)
          Catalog # End Of The Weak 001; A-side Matrix # EOW-12-SA
          End Of The Weak
        - Endgames - Love cares, 1983; SR-14123; Endgames (Box 256)
          Catalog # L33-1149; A-side Matrix # MCA-3706-ASR-1
        - Endemic Void - Yesterday was cool; Chronos, 1997; SR-14124; Endemic Void; Elixir (Box 256)
          Catalog # EVE 001; A-side Matrix # EVE-001-AA1
          Eves Records
        - Endgames - Building beauty, 1983; SR-14125; Endgames (Box 256)
          Catalog # VL 2269; A-side Matrix # VL-2269A
          Virgin
        - Enea, Laura - Can we find a way, 1996; SR-14126; Enea, Laura (Box 256)
          Catalog # MIC - 621; A-side Matrix # MIC-621-A
          Micmac Records, Inc.
        - Enemy Squad - Bob Dole is on drugs, 1996; SR-14127; Enemy Squad (Box 256)
          Catalog # USA 129701; A-side Matrix # USA-129701-A
          Tufamerica
        - Enemy Within - Support the miners, 1984; SR-14128; Enemy Within (Box 256)
          Catalog # RTT 151; A-side Matrix # RT 151 A1
          Rought Trade
        - Energetic - Real ganstas don't; So test me, 1996; SR-14129; Energetic (Box 256)
          Catalog # CEE 548; A-side Matrix # CEE 548-1A
          Cee-Low Entertainment
        - English Beat - Too nice to talk to; Best friend, 1983; SR-14130; English Beat (Box 257)
          Catalog # SP-70970; A-side Matrix # AM SP 070970-A RE-2 ES1
          I.R.S. Records
        - English Beat - Save it for later, 1982; SR-14131; English Beat (Box 257)
          Catalog # SP-70964; A-side Matrix # A&M SP070964A-T1
        - English, Barbara Jean - Dancing to keep from crying, 1979; SR-14132; English, Barbara Jean (Box 257)
          Catalog # ZK 100; A-side Matrix # ZK100
          Zakia records
        - Enigma - Sadness Part 1, 1990; SR-14133; Enigma (Box 257)
          Catalog # DINST 101; A-side Matrix # DINST 101 A-1U-1
          Australia
        - Enigma - Return to innocence, 1993; SR-14134; Enigma (Box 257)
          Catalog # Y-14122; A-side Matrix # 0777 7 14122 6 4
          Charisma
        - Enigma - Age of loneliness, 1994; SR-14135; Enigma (Box 257)
          Catalog # SPRO-14174; A-side Matrix # SPRO-14174-A1
        - Enoch, Ras - Money, 1984; SR-14136; Enoch, Ras (Box 257)
          Catalog # CR 102; A-side Matrix # CR-102A
          Jah's Records
        - Enriquez, Jocelyn - A little bit of ecstasy (Disc one), 1997; SR-14137; Enriquez, Jocelyn (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14138. Double album.
          Catalog # CLA-0190-0; A-side Matrix # CL-0190-A
          Classified Records
        - Enriquez, Jocelyn - A little bit of ecstasy (Disc two), 1997; SR-14138; Enriquez, Jocelyn (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14137. Double album.
          Catalog # CLA-0190-0; A-side Matrix # CL-0190-C
        - Ensemble - The game, 1990; SR-14139; Ensemble (Box 257)
          Different jacket. No entry in Discogs.
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # ME-17-A
        - Entouch - All nite, 1989; SR-14140; Entouch (Box 257)
          Catalog # 60858-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60858-A-1
        - Entouch - Crazay 4/U, 1990; SR-14141; Entouch (Box 257)
          Catalog # ED-5447; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-547-A-1
        - M.C. Cleiber & M.C. Fabinho - Rap da igualdade; O morro canta, 1995; SR-14142; M.C. Cleiber & M.C. Fabinho; Caramau (Box 257)
          Catalog # 443.055; A-side Matrix # 443 055 A
          Afegan
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Environmental Science - Plim-sould EP, 1997; SR-14143; Environmental Science (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14144. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 26; A-side Matrix # SKINT 26 A
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Environmental Science - Plim-sould EP, 1997; SR-14144; Environmental Science (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14143. Multiple copies.
        - Environmental Science - Coming home in a bodybag, 1997; SR-14145; Environmental Science (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14146. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 21; A-side Matrix # SKINT 21 A1
        - Environmental Science - Coming home in a bodybag, 1997; SR-14146; Environmental Science (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14145. Multiple copies.
        - Environmental Science - The day the zak stood still EP, 1998; SR-14147; Environmental Science (Box 257)
          Catalog # FABR012T; A-side Matrix # FABR 012T A
        - Environmental Science - Coming home in a bodybag, 1997; SR-14148; Environmental Science (Box 257)
        - Eon - Eon, 1975; SR-14149; Eon (Box 257)
          Catalog # SPS-5122; A-side Matrix # SPS-5122A-1A
          Scepter Records
        - Episode - Touch me (all night long), 1998; SR-14150; Episode (Box 257)
          Catalog # GC1000; A-side Matrix # GC-1000-A
          Golden Chip Records
        - EPMD - The big payback, 1989; SR-14151; EPMD (Box 257)
          Catalog # SBUK 17T; A-side Matrix # SBUK.17.(T).X1
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - EPMD - Back in busness (Disc one), 1997; SR-14152; EPMD (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14153. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 536 390-1; A-side Matrix # 314-536-390-1-A
          Def Jam Recordings
        - EPMD - Back in busness (Disc two), 1997; SR-14153; EPMD (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14152. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 536 391-1; A-side Matrix # 314-536-391-1-A
        - EPMD - Crossover (trunk mix), 1992; SR-14154; EPMD (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14155. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # OAS 4662; A-side Matrix # XSS-04662-A-1A
          Rush Associated Labels
        - EPMD - Crossover (trunk mix), 1992; SR-14155; EPMD (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14154. Multiple copies.
        - EPMD - The joint, 1997; SR-14156; EPMD (Box 257)
          Catalog # DEF 170-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-170-1-A
        - EPMD - So what cha sayin', 1998; SR-14157; EPMD (Box 257)
          Catalog # FRE-80133X; A-side Matrix # FRE-80133-X
          Fresh Records
        - EPMD - Crossover (trunk mix), 1992; SR-14158; EPMD (Box 257)
        - EQ - Let's make a move, 1987; SR-14159; EQ (Box 257)
          Catalog # DMD 1092; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-52485-1
        - Equals - Funky like a train, 1986; SR-14160; Equals (Box 257)
          Catalog # JABX 58; A-side Matrix # JABX-58-A2
          Club
        - Equator - Temperature Rising, 1996; SR-14161; Equator (Box 257)
          Catalog # DEM 12003; A-side Matrix # DEM 12003 A1
          Deus Ex Machina Records
        - Equator - Temperature Rising, 1996; SR-14162; Equator (Box 257)
        - Equitables - Carnival soca party, 1980; SR-14163; Equitables (Box 257)
          Catalog # GS 2226; A-side Matrix # GS2226A
          Straker's Records
        - Equitables - None stop party, 1983; SR-14164; Equitables (Box 257)
          Catalog # GS 2248; A-side Matrix # GS2248A
        - Erasure - Victim of love (limited edition remix), 1987; SR-14165; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-20740; A-side Matrix # 0-20740-A-SR1
          Sire
        - Erasure - Oh l'amour, 1986; SR-14166; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-20488; A-side Matrix # 0-20488-A-SH1
        - Erasure - Drama!, 1989; SR-14167; Erasure (Box 257)